What I would like to learn is the
7th grade.
We have to give them the correct execution.
This is about the new stages of
meditation. In a meditation career,
the development of a meditation is
the new steps. 9 very typical
levels. When I was a child, I
still had the generation that grew up.
The roads here are long, hundreds of
kilometers. The ones that ever came to surf there in Germany are
eight
hours' drive to Los Angeles in eleven hours.
Now with my mother, my father,
four of us were locked in a car.
We talked to each other the whole time. Go the whole way.
Father asked,
we are almost there. Almost
there, only seven hours and 45
minutes to 15 minutes more. After 15 minutes,
a little bit asked, "Are you
there yet?" Yes, that is. And the children
always ask this question. Do they know you're
there yet? Later we learned
to read the two. Hunters 3,156
km, ten-year-olds 3,146 kilometers. In
meditation, it is very helpful if
someone can tell you how you know how to
progress. Up to today, you still have to go.
These are the  Signs of the highway
for meditation. There are nine
highway signs that I will teach you today.
This is very traditional. They come
from... Can you read the book on meditation?
Levels of meditation. There are nine
basic levels or stages.
Why I like to teach. It
's easy to measure.
It's very easy to measure, like for
the diamonds from the sale. Too much
money have you made?
This is a number, and you
know you've come. But with inner
progress, how far is compassion?
How many kilometers of compassion? House
daily. Up to 99% compassion. 40 percent
guided. How patient are you?
The yoga teachers kill you.
Patient. What is your number? 43, 35, 52.
It's very difficult to give a number to
inner progress. The
progress of one's heart is... But
in meditation, I was lucky. There are
nine highways. We got
further. And then you can
judge how far we can...
Now the peri... You can
estimate how... Vertical Combat A0F6MD...
Fun at the job... With the teacher, the
concrete brings...  For example, in a country station,
and the teacher chooses another
person from this team who is sick or
unhappy, or they have problems with their
husband or wife. They want someone to think about.
Then choose someone,
for example, a friend. For a few
seconds,
you think about your money. This is level
number one
because for a few seconds, keep your mind on
this person and immediately think about the
lunch. The bachelor today
also finishes earlier.
How do you think about other things? This
meditation, as well as his for one second,
6 hellos, goodbyes, gladly, sound, batteries, the one
your wife gives, then way to work.
You do this story, you have to know,
and it's when you do your job,
bring the mind subject, and then
start to be distracted. But it's
progress, the very important factor.
This is number one of nine. The sausage is
that you listened to your teacher.
You got instructions from a teacher.
Number one assumes that you
went to a class and your
teacher gave the meditation object.
The teacher has  They said, 'Think of
someone who is in trouble in
their life.
We often say that level number
one is reached when you
ask the teacher what you should meditate on.
It's already a lot of progress. That
's a very short period of time. If you
compare that time with the
comparison during which the person
thinks they have the problem and the time they
have would be lunch, you think that
ten percent is 90 percent. Which is
lunch? 90 percent. That's not
true.
You can do that ten percent. That's not what's
bad. It's
a start.
It's not worthless. It's very, very
rare that your good
meditation teacher is. It's
incredibly difficult to
meet a good meditation teacher. When you
've reached level number one, then
you're already one person in a
million. Decides, especially in a scene, a
very special person. Don't think that
the butcher meditates or up to 19
percent of their, who so far are better than a
million people, at least to have started
to meditate.
People who don't meditate know people who
never had a good meditation teacher.  Meeting
teachers is like meeting people who
never learn to read. It's very, very similar.
They're very, very similar.
If you don't have the good chamber to meet a
really good meditation teacher, it
's almost like never
learning to read. Here's a whole life going on,
believing this thing, and the
chance of that thing, I have no idea why, I have no
idea what it says, what's written in there
is like you're blind. Who is that? A
form of blindness, what are they good for?
But these are just strange
forms, and to escape that, I have no idea
what they mean.
I imagine your mother and a
father, who is a dear teacher, would
never have sent you to school, would
never have taught you to
read,
and you can't read. People who ca
n't media, people who
meet meditation teachers, they
are very, very similar to people who ca
n't read, but can solve the problem.
The team remained its form of blindness.
If you're level number one, only ten
percent of which 96 percent of
lunch hamburgers have
vegetarian burgers, then you are very, very, very much like that.
Incredibly lucky and
you are something very special. You are
cool or uncool for junk train
[Music]
two kids job now you are able
to stay on the meditation path. What
is that meditation spect? A friend of
difficulties is
you have once right is slowly
further
whose mother Berlin traditionally
you connect the third finger of the
left hand must practice this. Moreover, it was
long how do you not use a
usual right hand and a thumb?
That he is laziness. There are
special planners in this film.
For this reason, the cook seedling is
here practicing
using his left hand, but that
Mahler to release the third and fourth
fingers and then counts to make
a movement like loud church Michael.
We say if there is a spirit in the room
then the spirit should be able
to constantly hear because there is always yesterday
in the room. There are a few gestures in the
room that don't somehow know what. What you
can do is this position. There is
everywhere. Board. There are many
Peters in this country. Here, this country
was a war zone.
Many populations died here and
The guests are therefore not normal,
they all have hearing aids or
normal, but it is traditional
to say it loudly enough so that a guest next to the person eating has to
understand you. It's crazy,
if you can keep your mind on that person for
as long as
it takes, 108 of their normal speech,
then you have reached level number two.
Normal is a premium,
someone can check how long
that takes, 1-2 minutes,
maybe a minute. If she
can keep her mind on that person for a minute without thinking about lunch,
then you have reached level number two.
Checking is therefore impossible for girls, they
almost always think about food,
that's with every breath.
Admittedly, but you can check that,
which means it takes many years
to learn, many years to observe a mind,
many years in
practice to notice when your mind
is not on the object. It is very difficult
to use the mind train to check the mind. The mind is
tired, has problems
checking the mind.
I understand, it's very difficult. That
takes a lot of practice and
catching yourself when  You
start thinking about a military mistake,
it's difficult but try. My
teacher,
when we made the teeth out of covers,
says something else. Think, start
again at 1. I have something like that. Is there anything with
breakfast? 12. What films about breakfast at
church? Yes, I think half an hour.
I didn't even get to the
two. How honest,
how honest are you with yourself?
Happy, not who, who lied to me.
You lied to yourself and
lied to yourself.
I have the hamburger, but not too
much. The 123,
I don't choose, so to speak, takes them in
old trains, promoted. Start, try it for
five minutes.
If you get to three, you're very
lucky. If you get to year 3, it's
dishonest.
He has many years of practice and I'm
doing strength here because I'm jealous of
the other teachers. Then I
usually break the problem while I'm doing
the strength. I admit that I
'm simply addicted and then
I become a helper again during the confession.
The THW with
meditation to count up to ten if
they are a  You can keep your mind on the object for as
long as is unusual, by the way.
I would say if you can keep your
mind on the object for half a rosary,
then that would be a sign
that you are the best entrepreneur because you
can be. Focus will
show in a normal life.
The best mother, the best
entrepreneur is a yoga teacher. Focus
means
unknowingly whether you have really
reached level number two. Such a
person is already one of the best
entrepreneurs in their city, something along
those lines. That much focus. Normal
people don't have more than two or three
breaths of focus. Now, how can you keep your mind on
something for two minutes?
Then you can invent an iPhone.
Most people get there.
Most people in a whole lifetime
never get that far. Don't think that
level is something stupid. Level
number two is cool.
That is already an incredible
entrepreneur, an incredible mother, or an
incredibly mean question. You cook
best.
That means everyone else... Yes, that has
n't been forgotten either. Otherwise, that takes a lot of
focus and to come well. That's why
they called me a pot burner. A
lamb didn't have me anymore.
My head called me a trainer
because I always thought that one had burned it.
I despise remembering I had cooked, finally
not thrown out of
the church. Because if your lama
makes you cook, then if everything is for
eight years,
then they throw you out. Then
you can study how far you are at the
new level, how the world's greatest
Pattinson levels have come. That depends on
how tired you are and how much you are
busy. Guesthouse, two cases of
meditation, busier mentally, again and again gestures at
all levels, while judged
by how much you are busy
yesterday, how much more tired now. That
time is the magic, braver
she is. Have you thought of the guests? It's
dangerous if you think you're meditating
that she's not moving for half an hour.
Everything is just that, but you're just
sluggish and tired.
Many, many people who meditate for too long are just
tired without
snoring.
One day I really banged my head
hard on the goods.
I fell completely asleep.
Then it comes down to the wall. So far, it's been up to the
military.
During the first Bernie, what
percentage of the time are you  You tired
spirits, the busy business has
traveled, thinking about what I have to do
after meditation, is the big
fan of meditation, we have to do this,
meditation is used up, we are
twelve minutes ago, two weeks ago, the beast thinking
about all these things, what has to be done, what
is busy mind, tired spirits, careful, this doesn't feel
like meditation, the percentage of your
mind,
even if you think about that, we, the person
Tom Klemm, how much percentage of his
gas, busy mind, how much
percentage in the first levels, 100 percent,
comes the property, the
quality of meditation, yoga positions
in the same constellation, really good at
the high quality,
you can really do them sloppily
because it's a little crooked,
and so on, the breathing, I think you,
that lunch, meditation with high
quality on the first band levels, I
am 1.0,
that say maybe, maybe I can't
remember anything that a
person should think about, but the
properties of meditation are
definitely known, with glass, definitely a
small Volkswagen, cheap, is also
not very good, that's okay, most
essential
meditation needs  Yoga and meditation
take time to progress;
it doesn't come quickly. Everyone believes that
when they start yoga,
they will do what the young teacher
does, but that takes years. Your body
opens very slowly, the mind
opens even more slowly. But you try,
you tried yesterday, that's another
two hours. Job means, at the
request, a little flow. Time is
needed to paint a wound,
90 seconds, depends on how
fast, normal,
and also on how long the mantra
is.
[Music]
We're talking about my naming, okay, do
n't worry, level number three, how much
occupy mind and how much tired, gain level,
single, where two almost all the
time, even when a person
thinks, half of your mind
still thinks about lunch, says long,
the jogger distracts, the job, it took me a few
years to
understand that, working in countries means a
stain on his clothes, is a piece of fabric
on the clothes,
usually make a hole here at
the knees, and if you know a good one faster,
then you can do that from the eat in side the  A
piece of fabric, a piece of
fabric from the Isar 1, and sewing that you
[music]
how should I say that? I
usually understood it because I
thought
the meditation goes on and on and on,
then a part comes when you're away from the object,
then you react,
you come away, then back again. But some
people say that the spot
is the tent at the object, the time at the object, the
tracks, the teams, two years, and then
you get a piece of fabric, and
some people say now it would already be up to
6. That means short times at the object,
mostly
when you've reached an apartment, you
do ten minutes of meditation, and
then you lose it for two minutes,
then you come back, usually again ten
minutes. It's more time at the object than away from the
object, more time at the
object, away. That takes a spot, that
means you lose the work for its
time, which puts where it is in Potsdam,
but in this case, it prepares
something, isn't, isn't there, there's a
short distance when it's not moving,
that's called then it comes
back for minutes and then it leaves again for two
minutes.  Then comes the 20,000
back, the sign of Ivo number three
is more time at the object, Greeks to
currently six,
that means an apartment, number 1, number 2 is
more far away from the work, that a
famous lecture on meditation, I
say, I can describe everything in words,
I can't describe everything in
words, you have to
try it out, I
can give you some tips, I
can give the rules, but the real
meditation learning and teaching is that you have to
grasp it in your own eyes. There are
things about meditation that
someone can only do in the rain, just the time at the
meditation place, and then learned. I ca
n't teach you everything about meditation
to touch it yourself
because every person has a
different experience. I can
describe things,
describe them, but from the words
alone you can't get the full
meaning, you have to
try it yourself.
It's a very famous meditation
construct. Now let's
go to level number four,
which is called saying that you're at the
object all the time, but with poor
quality, you understand, yes, you're at it all the time.
Object and subject hold for ten
minutes, 20 minutes, the power stays off,
but the quality of attention is
not very good. There is still a lot of
tiredness. There is
n't always a lot of thinking
about other things, but you don't lose the
object.
It becomes gray and clear, like heavy
rain when you drive. You ca
n't see through the glass clearly, but you
see what it is. It's the lights of the
car in front of you, but it's not very
clear. The property isn't very good,
but you don't lose the object anymore.
Who is in that? It's the lights of the car in front of
you, but it's not clear.
That's level number four. You don't
lose the object, but not very
strongly. My writings say once, it's
bad to hold, and black and white, it falls
easily. That
once it falls down. That's
level number four.
You don't forget it, but it's
leaving the stage. It's close to
losing it. You understand, you don't lose it.
She lets the outer, the marker, not
drop, but that almost. It slipped out of her
hand, and the property isn't
very good.
That's a difficult thing.  is
not focused, set up so that my
things are seen, but it's not in small
print.
The focus isn't very good. That's
level.
Why is the trait bad if
you still have a busy and tired
guest? But it's not too
serious that the object actually
loses. 4 is pretty cool.
That means you are.
Is the better meditator than 100 other
meditators? If you can get to level
number four in this life,
then you are. But we want to
control it. It's called level number 51.
You are the boss of your own mind,
and you have something. Czechs say it's like
he breaks it down into small cracks. The one that sits in the back of my
head. That happens to me, and already there's
a small buffer sitting here. The
order of the observed yesterday was rather a
problem. Then he pushes the room.
BBC,
that's already called a Zen meditation
stool. That you develop,
I won't. You even learn to
prepare the breathing or balloons in that
direction. But if you meditate and
develop a rush,
this Roland observes the rest of the
mind, and when the mind
sits thinking about Hamburg, the g
onions or you get tired then is the
feeling when the apartment has five you have
rhythms schechen the muscle fear
is strong in the good reputation lanz
what is from that possibility or all
things to think the developer is a
special muscle in your mind who
says you will lose the object now
if you continue very carefully I
can see that you me you will was on
question said Sheen was on random 20
dollars
let's cancel that that
is itself says Czech Republic itself
the smoke alarm
[Music]
that leave there are
many cowboys around here
who actually carry weapons in this
town that was who go with weapons into
a restaurant or cafe
it was an ice cream shop back then I took
mine in such a friend took hers these the
guys they came in with the weapons
and he next opponent had
went that movie
no that's not a movie it's real
we really have weapons hold the moon
then they have a special be they
know the key to start with them in
decathlete means the rope around the
head  The short swing and then
to pull in the crew, what is one from the
cow, his attention,
there are two mental functions to
develop, must for meditation, says
master,
twice already, it was very nice, means
that is prepared, the
cowboy's rope, then you bring, go
back, the main begins to think about the negotiation, did
n't say that the
Camaro is, yes, water over there,
he has thought about the way home,
okay, I have him, comes back, comes back, comes back,
comes back,
you need a  So, both have a smoker
and a coffee, even from a
café,
that's just 54, which is strong, the
Czechs 295 is very strong,
the medi mind has 21, or whatever
performance they hold at the head and it runs
and with the head against were falls, is
the obvious medi mind, if
the meditation hasn't fallen asleep, this
means that they are no longer the animal,
everything happens to everyone, the
obvious inertia,
they want on the 5,
you have this obvious
inertia, lived over, it's no longer
possible that you completely last the
meditation,
but there is a subtle tiredness,
I look good, right, but you think
that something else is thinking,
not really about the person, you have a problem,
you just look good, more subtle, is
very, very dangerous, very, very
dangerous, feels like
the meditation, and I assume 90
percent of all people meditate who can't, ca
n't have this training, have to
count, inert mind, mostly
they would have known that not even everything,
carefully, that is the really
dangerous fractures,
only running the head and there were  To
hit, there is evidence, you will
have a bump, subtle inertia, you have it for
many years and you don't know
that you have it, if you
meditate for too long, more than ten
minutes at the beginning, then I will say
it is guaranteed, it is the subtle, that
means that people who
meditate for two hours get it, forget it, impossible,
I have been meditating for 50 years now, it is
not possible, if you can do one hour, that
is enough, that without you getting
tired, you are there, you don't even have that, it
often doesn't work, which yes, so far
accepted object, that's why it is so
dangerous,
that means you didn't think of anyone, sick person,
yes, what is the quality of
meditation, high, what is a high quality
meditation, in business class
meditation, one or
two corners meditation, first tired,
you must always ask what is the
quality of meditation, all of them, that is
the quality of focus, what is the quality
of attention,
how good is the meditation, you can do
your yoga poses over and over again for years
and it is not
correct, and the lamp is a position
with a lot of attention, care and
long pressure, and that is then
completely different,
that is a  You
obviously don't have an apartment. Rain yesterday.
You obviously have
dangerous tired spirits. Level number
five. This level is called
controlling the guests. I'm going to
say the name now. I would have checked it in the notes
where number one doesn't
put the spirit off the subject,
just very briefly, like when you're a woman. These are
for seeing each other again. Coast and
somehow work to work. Not,
but I know fixed when she's in her
kitchen. Number two, my lord, form of
continuity.
How about if this is a level? Number
two is a painter. As long as I can
keep the object,
number three, the stains in
meditation. From which meditation path grows.
Next approach, but a few stains
of project work. This is an apartment. 3, 4
[Music]
The new object is stuck on, but with
bad theme pictures clarify
the apartment. Over 40, cheaper, clever, because it is,
but wakes up, or glue is
n't so good that losing it. This is another
4.
Please write. Came a master. Can one
playfully have changed something?
Maybe we'll get problems. Apartment,
you are  You have lost control of your
mind, not very good
control.
You don't have the obviously active
mind, at least not that you have so much
control.
You can say you don't sleep anymore,
dreaming. Yes, that's the next thing, ca
n't let go. I said Reimann. The year
stands, the day will come, is really
sorry, but not asleep. Okay,
confirm.
[Music]
Every person, all Chinese people, Chinese people,
not in it. I have started.
[Music]
He asks what you do with 66. Is something on the
finger really wanted here?
This prepares peaceful, more peaceful guests.
[Music]
Extremely strong, the smoke alarm is
sensitized from the point of view of sitting. Someone
comes in, needs a cigarette, and
the alarm goes off because someone gets
angry and a little bit too comes out of
their ears. Part of the alarm goes off.
I don't cut it very powerfully. Apartments,
what do we have to do now? Yes, 6. I do
n't have it very powerfully.
Now I have to understand this, and
we have talked about this very often. That
means students know this: when you drive your car,
then a new person will
hold the steering wheel, completely
tense, completely stiff, and  Then the
car goes a little more to the left,
then they hold it nicely with me, not any
further.
If you then learn to drive a car accordingly,
then you learn left and
autocorrect all the time. The
way it works is that when
the car goes to the left, curiosity to the right,
and then the car starts to veer to the right,
and you go to the left. After a
year of this procedure, it's automatic. You do
n't think about talking to your friend anymore.
You can't even use your hands
today because the dental thing is,
if you have to know, you hold, then
it goes very slowly off, so the left side has to
correct.
But the nature of correcting something
is to make corrections.
This is useful
knowledge. Now too far to the left, and then
you go too far to the right, and then
left, right, and therefore, if you have the hands of a
fiber that the gentlemen never stop to
correct, and worse, three
procedures hardly move. A good
driver moves a
little all the time, so many other things at the same time.
The hand moves, someone does
n't think about meditation, it's
financially going around, but in
meditation we have to
correct the meditation.
The knowledge media, you are me, you will me, okay, what should
I  Then what would be done
now is to speak if we
do the Roosters' Easter program.
There is a way
to get the car back, but usually
you go too far away.
Then you have to try to get a little more tired.
Therefore, in meditation, you must have
an autopilot of correction all the time. Are
you now our camp? Subtle, subtle,
busy guest to recognize
what the word is so that I get to 40 dollars?
What is the general one from Alaska? It's
called water under which it
can go when the river tributaries,
but the
water doesn't always flow underneath.
The peaks count, so that trains
go, but the water flows underneath a
little, which means
these stable businesses are eaten. You do
n't always think about what you have to do today,
but on another level, so many ranks where
you hold, the mind is always 344
million Germans between the steps
to do, but the whole thing feels under
the ice because money doesn't speak, but
it is already. You are preparing
to bring the Gaisberg ahead. It
is water and an iron
spring day that will get warmer, and that
is already  It's gotten to the point where the ice
breaks and the water level rises. Have you
really ended that? A suppressed one,
only, and it always flows through me eventually, only
underneath. It's like
when someone you love dies. It closes that
under the mind for you. It
speaks then a
few times a day. Do you want to
think about it, and then it focuses on these three. The
pain doesn't go away; it only covers it.
Then it breaks out again. The subtle one
is so busy, so many things to do
today, even investments in glass
and metal. It's so strong, yet
her medication is probably good. It's on your
mind. The meeting at 6 o'clock is a
big fight with a husband. Two
weeks. It's like seeing your guests. You'd
rather break out.
So many business matters become
the tenth worry. Is there anything like that?
That someone has been
laid to sleep or someone has died?
Because you live, you lose then. Yes, but
the worries of ours mostly... that's called
so many busy people. He is what I... so
many carriers, or when this day is
simply... there is a quality of
attention. Do
you understand here? This is an apartment
when she was 6
From the 6th onwards, there's
not only a lot of danger that too
many carriers are triggered,
you've brought peace to level number six,
and peace to the tired spirits, whether we
obviously neither yesterday when the
apartment 16 was gone, the only thing you have to worry about
is when a day's carrier
comes, a daily plan, meters out, you say shut up,
but the fleece still gets through, always
in your mind, into
apartment 6, what's gone, the
entire route, attention, or
maybe that expresses itself as a very strong
plan on the benches, know
guests again, maybe the plan is for, would have,
that the plan of the day is, the
surface comes when you're seven,
complete peace, what happens when
the apartment on the 7th,
guess, a busy one, more guests,
no form of busy, first one, more,
yes, no great danger for subtle
busy ones, or they serve,
maybe there's a small danger
somewhere, no great danger,
and only associations, live, massive, said
Sheila, now the room alarm and a
cowboy outfit, not perfect,
strong smoke alarm,
I hardly thank, explain, if something
goes wrong then  It comes directly to the
operations and you can immediately
withdraw your money
because what does it also mean to
remember
many people have translated that wrong
again a collection that's not it
it just means withdraws money
to move
we all have to throw the goals out
to Kabul with suits how many have
only given me the focused 1 focused
mind what does 1 focused mean is to
become a strong money maybe that will
now be a mountain and I say
an object and do you think a laser that does
n't mean that it means the
training stays on an object and does
n't move from it complete 1
justice that guests so further away will
not be a meter mind and a busy
guest in any form at this
point this conversation is how often do you have to
correct
how often do you have to adjust things how often do
you have to adjust things
at level a that is the only question
that often during the meditation station you
have to make corrections in a
yesterday the answer is once
when you start meditating
you have to tweak it a bit, adjust it
I'm a bit megabit I'm a
bit busy until you finish the first few
minutes  Dual all the
adjustments then you flow there but the
whole beginning from the pair a little
more of that a little less of theirs that
up and that fit and then
it's really like in the airplane you
see you're finished quite a
beautiful one with a straight line okay
after the initial
adjustment understands what I mean animals
no time because what to adjust everything
perfect they very well beautiful
maybe now is now once a
year sits down and therefore to the
object they are beautiful
it takes a lot of time don't worry
but there will come a time
when the bus has to translate you have to
take your word you will have the most annoying one
it is done
that is really a meditation the
name of it is negative meditation
youtube and that is what you need to see
teacher has directly explained it
is a long journey doesn't happen in a
day or a week or a month
there are all these romantic
stories from the young mine that went out
and chopped wood have
more to see those are not correct
it takes a lot but it takes years
start simply I don't
worry that yoga I come every day
when you don't worry whether you can do it
or not  I can't think about it,
I come from real against day, that's
all, then I won't let the
teacher beat up or
crumble so that something better,
just come every day, the rest of
this level are in this way,
especially in the curves, talk about it.
[Music]
Making the poster, that would be very nice,
maybe I'll try that sometime, where to
make the poster, I don't know, let's
mostly, it would be nice
if we made the whole poster,
I did that once.
[Music]
Maybe we'll do that if it's just for
fun, because we don't like that, because we wo
n't finish the house, the rest of it,
but it would be a lot of fun, let's
try that sometime, let's make
this training
completely
explode, if we have time, I realize, I
make it fun, are they
teasing me a little?
[Music]
That's it, I think, we have
traffic today, that this one minute
left, makes the prayer, are there
any people in a coat,
can you have a suggestion for that, if you
want to look good, tell me the first
two words loudly, Stasi, and then
he made the rest, no thought,
we'll make a monastery.  Boys
are the ones in Sakhir, mama mama, that's
called VA. There's
a word for it, you just need to
pronounce the first two values ​​correctly.
Here you see very loudly a second,
first two judoka flashing,
they say each [
Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
In my house I try to know,
then I can have my half lotus during
dinner with the one, then I do it
with the other.
You can do the full lotte, and
learn for months if you, if you are on
this axis, the backs of the chairs
where we have it, one foot makes that
the habit. If you need it on the plane,
you really are. That's one of
the reasons for it.
[Music]